Inventory of the National Cattlemen’s Association records, 1898-2018
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Subject Files, Series VI.
  - Animal Agriculture: Research to Meet Human Needs in the 21st Century, 1979-1981 (Box 197, Folder 18)
  - Animal Agriculture Seminar, 1963 (Box 197, Folders 19-22)
  - Animal Biologics Act of 1979 (Box 197, Folder 23)
  - Animal Disease Laboratory, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 24)
  - Animal Diseases, 1982 (Box 197, Folder 25)
  - Animal Drugs, 1980, 1982 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Animal Health, 1979-1981 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Animal Health Institute, 1982-1988 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Animal Refeeding, 1980 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Animal Rights, 1979-1982 (Box 198, Folders 5-11)
  - Animal Welfare, 1981 (Box 198, Folder 12)
  - Animal Welfare Act Amendments, 1977 (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - 19th Annual Democratic Dinner, 1982 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - 7th Annual Farm Forum, 1986 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Antibiotics, 1977, 1981 (Box 199, Folders 3-9)
  - Antitrust, 1975-1976 (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Appalachian Regional Development Act, 1964 (Box 199, Folders 11-13)
  - Argentina-Tierra del Fuego, 1941-1946 (Box 199, Folders 14-15)
  - Argentine Sanitary Commission, 1937-1944 (Box 199, Folder 16)
  - Argentine Sanitary Convention, 1935-1944, 1946 (Box 199, Folders 17-22)
  - Arizona, 1948, 1956, 1958-1959, undated (Box 199, Folders 23-25)
  - Arizona, 1955-1957 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Arizona National Livestock Show-1956 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Arizona Watershed Program, 1958-1960 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Armour and Company, 1955-1960 (Box 200, Folders 4-5)
  - Asian Journalists, 1988 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Associated Milk Producers, Inc., 1986 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Association of National Grasslands, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Association Programs-Preconditioning Livestock, 1964-1971 (Box 200, Folders 9-13)
  - Association Programs-Preconditioning Livestock, 1966-1973 (Box 201, Folders 1-5)
  - Audio Tape Service, 1952-1954 (Box 201, Folders 6-10)
  - Australia, 1964-1970, 1977-1981 (Box 202, Folders 1-11)
  - Australian Beef Industry on Display, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - Australian Meat and Livestock Corp, 1981-1985 (Box 202, Folder 13)
  - Australian Meat Board, 1964 (Box 202, Folder 14)
  - Australian Meat Board, 1963-1969 (Box 203, Folders 1-3)
  - Australians in Denver, 1987 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Automobile Window Stickers, 1960-1961 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Awards, 1950s-1960s, undated (Box 203, Folders 6-9)
  - Barrett, Sen. Frank A., 1955-1957 (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Barron’s, 1964-1965 (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - Beef-Dan Murphy Company, 1980-1981 (Box 203, Folder 12)
  - Beef and Vegetable Campaign, 1954 (Box 203, Folders 13-16)
  - Beef Bacon, 1955-1956 (Box 203, Folder 17)
  - Beef Bacon, 1954-1956 (Box 204, Folders 1-2)
  - Beef Cattle Research, 1953 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Beef Cattle Survey, 1965 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Beef Check-Off, 1975-1978 (Box 686, Folder 16)
  - Beef Empire Days Award, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Beef Grading, 1930-1962, 1981-1982, undated (Box 204, Folders 6-15)
  - Beef Grading, 1930-1960s, 1980-1982, undated (Box 205, Folders 1-13)
  - Beef Grading, 1936, 1950-1961, 1981-1982 (Box 206, Folders 1-5)
  - Beef Grading-Editorial Data, 1955, undated (Box 206, Folders 6-12)
  - Beef Improvement Conference, 1965 (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - Beef Improvement Federation, 1968-1969 (Box 206, Folders 14-17)
  - Beef Imports, 1964-1977, undated (Box 206, Folders 18-22)
  - Beef Imports, 1964-1977 (Box 207, Folders 1-4)
  - Beef Improvement Federation, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Beef Industry Information, 1952 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Beef Industry Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Beef Industry Tour, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Beef Prices, 1980 (Box 207, Folders 9-12)
  - Beef Production, 1981 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Beef Promotion, 1953-1968, undated (Box 208, Folders 2-10)
  - Beef Promotion, 1953-1969, 1980, undated (Box 209, Folders 1-17)
  - Beef Promotion, 1935-1968, 1980 (Box 210, Folders 1-23)
  - Beef Promotion, 1953-1957, 1979-1980 (Box 211, Folders 1-10)
  - Beef Tariff, 1946 (Box 211, Folder 11)
  - Beef Technology, 1981 (Box 211, Folder 12)
  - Beef Update Seminar, 1986 (Box 211, Folder 13)
  - Beeferendum, 1976-1980 (Box 211, Folders 14-19)
  - Beefmaster Breeders Universal, 1985-1988 (Box 211, Folder 20)
  - Beresford, Rex, undated (Box 211, Folder 21)
  - Better Communications, 1981 (Box 211, Folder 22)
  - Big Game Animals, 1944-1957, undated (Box 211, Folders 23-28)
  - Big Piney Bull Project Broadcast, 1955 (Box 211, Folder 29)
  - Block, John R., 1985 (Box 211, Folder 30)
  - Bluetongue, 1975 (Box 211, Folder 31)
  - Bowes Company, 1968-1969 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scouts of America-1960 Boy Scout Jamboree (Box 212, Folders 2-5)
  - Boycotts, 1966-1967 (Box 212, Folders 6-8)
  - Boycotts, 1969 (Box 686, Folders 17)
  - Brand Inspection, 1953 (Box 212, Folders 9-10)
  - Branding, 1959-1963, undated (Box 212, Folders 11-13)
  - Brands, 1939, 1957, undated (Box 212, Folders 14-16)
  - Brannan Farm Plan, 1947-1951 (Box 212, Folders 17-20)
  - Breeder’s Gazette, 1955 (Box 212, Folders 21-22)
  - Broadcasting, 1961-1964, 1968, undated (Box 212, Folders 23-25)
  - Broadcasting, 1961-1962, 1964 (Box 213, Folders 1-2)
  - Brucellosis, 1980 (Box 213, Folders 3-4)
  - Brucellosis (Bang’s Disease), 1947-1949 (Box 213, Folders 5-7)
  - Brucellosis, 1956 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - Brucellosis-New Regulations, 1955 (Box 213, Folders 9-10)
  - Brucellosis-Uniform Methods, 1981 (Box 213, Folder 11)
  - Brucellosis Questionnaire, 1954-1955 (Box 213, Folders 12-15)
  - Brucellosis Testing, Data, 1954-1955 (Box 213, Folder 16)
  - Building, 1954-1955 (Box 213, Folders 17-19)
  - Building, 1954-1957 (Box 214, Folders 1-4)
  - Bull Beef Symposium, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - Bush, George H.W, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Buy American, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Byproduct Feeds, 1974-1975 (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - California State Board of Food and Agriculture, 1985 (Box 214, Folder 9)
  - Canada, 1973-1981 (Box 214, Folders 10-14)
  - Canadian Cattlemen’s Association, 1981-1986 (Box 214, Folder 15)
  - Canadian Grading System Letter and the USDA, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 16)
  - Canadian Trade Agreement, Memorandum, 1938 (Box 214, Folder 17)
  - Canned and Cooked Meat Importers Association, 1985 (Box 214, Folder 18)
  - Capital Gains in Cattle Numbers, 1953-1955 (Box 214, Folder 19)
  - Carcass, 1967-1979 (Box 214, Folder 20)
  - Carry-Over Basis, 1979-1980 (Box 214, Folder 21)
  - Letter of Dan C. Casement, Kansas, 1934 (Box 214, Folder 22)
  - Cattle, 1950 (Box 214, Folder 23)
  - Cattle-Holstein Friesian, undated (Box 214, Folder 24)
  - Cattle Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box 214, Folder 25)
  - Cattle and Beef Futures, 1964-1967, undated (Box 214, Folders 26-31)
  - Cattle Council of Australia, 1981, 1983 (Box 214, Folder 32)
  - Cattle Feeding, 1981 (Box 214, Folder 33)
  - Cattle Feeding Manuals - Economic Data and Analysis, 1962-1968 (Box 686, Folder 18)
  - Cattle Figures, 1955-1968 (Box 215, Folders 1-2)
  - Cattle Hide Tariff, 1929 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Cattle in National Forests, 1930s (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - Cattlemen’s Beef Promotion and Research Board, 1986-1987 (Box 215, Folders 5-9)
  - Cattlemen’s Beef Promotion and Research Board, 1986-1987 (Box 216, Folders 1-2)
  - Cattlemen’s Board, 1986 (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Cattlemen’s Leadership Conference, 1976-1977 (Box 216, Folders 4-6)
  - Cella, Chester-Clark Jewelry Company, Tie Clasps, 1955-1956 (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - Central Bank for Cooperatives, 1982 (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - Central Georgia Soil and Water Conservation Banquet, 1985-1986 (Box 216, Folder 9)
  - Central Soya, 1988 (Box 216, Folder 10)
  - Cervi’s Rocky Mountain Journal, 1963-1964 (Box 216, Folder 11)
  - Chemical Pesticides Coordination Act-H.R. 12419 and S. 3473, 1960 (Box 216, Folders 12-15)
  - Chicago Mercantile Exchange, 1981-1986 (Box 216, Folder 16)
  - China, 1979-1981 (Box 216, Folder 17)
  - Cholesterol Information-Argentina, Australia, Uruguay, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 18)
  - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 19)
  - William P. Clark, Secretary of the Interior, 1981-1983 (Box 216, Folder 20)
  - Clear Channel Broadcasting, 1962-1977 (Box 686, Folder 19-21)
  - Clear Channel Broadcasting, 1977-1979 (Box 687, Folder 1)
  - Clear Channel Broadcasting, 1977 (Box 216, Folder 21)
  - Clear Title, 1984 (Box 216, Folder 22)
  - Colorado Department of Game, Fish, and Parks, 1968 (Box 216, Folder 23)
  - Colorado Marketing Seminar, 1981 (Box 216, Folder 24)
  - Colorado Society of Association Executives, 1988 (Box 216, Folder 25)
  - Colorado State University, 1983 (Box 216, Folder 26)
  - Commission on Agricultural Credit, 1969 (Box 216, Folder 27)
  - Commission on Agricultural Credit, 1969 (Box 217, Folders 1-4)
  - Committee for Reciprocity Information, 1941, 1947 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Committees-U.S. Congress, 1981 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Commodities Prices, 1944 (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - Commodity Coordinating Group, 1978 (Box 217, Folder 8)
  - Commodity Credit Corporation-Disposition of Feed Grains, 1961-1975 (Box 217, Folder 9)
  - Commodity Futures Trading Commission-Hearings on Proposed Rules, 1975 (Box 217, Folder 10)
  - Commodity Futures Trading Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 217, Folders 11-15)
  - Commodity Futures Trading Commission-Hearings on Proposed Rules, 1975-1976 (Box 217, Folders 16-19)
  - Commodity Group Meeting, 1982-1983 (Box 218, Folders 1-2)
  - Commodity Roundtable, 1984-1987 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Commodity Trading, 1964-1977, undated (Box 218, Folders 4-13)
  - Commodity Trading, 1966-1977 (Box 219, Folders 1-4)
  - Communications, 1978 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Computers (Word Processing), 1983-1984 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Concerned Cattlemen Task Force, 1977 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Confederacion Interamericana de Ganaderos (Inter-American Cattlemen’s Confederation), 1965-1969, undated (Box 219, Folders 8-14)
  - Confederacion Interamericana de Ganaderos (Inter-American Cattlemen’s Confederation), 1966-1969, 1982 (Box 220, Folders 1-11)
  - Confederacion Nacional Ganadera, 1988 (Box 220, Folder 12)
  - Conference on Australian and New Zealand Imports, 1962 (Box 220, Folder 13)
  - Conference on Australian and New Zealand Imports, 1962-1963 (Box 221, Folders 1-5)
  - Confinement Feeding, 1970-1971 (Box 221, Folders 6-9)
  - Congress-Voting Records, 1979-1981 (Box 221, Folder 10)
  - 1978 Congressional Actions (Box 221, Folder 11)
  - 1980 Congressional Appropriations, 1979-1980 (Box 221, Folder 12)
  - 1978 Congressional Elections (Box 221, Folder 13)
  - Congressional Questions, 1980 (Box 221, Folder 14)
  - Conservation, 1955-1956, undated (Box 221, Folders 15-18)
  - Consumer Preference Studies, 1956 (Box 221, Folder 19)
  - Consumer Relations, 1982 (Box 221, Folder 20)
  - Co-op Farming, 1945-1969 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative Livestock Commission Company, 1926 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Coordinated Beef Improvement Conference-1961, 1961-1962, undated (Box 222, Folders 3-9)
  - Coordinated Beef Improvement Conference-1963, 1962-1964 (Box 222, Folders 10-17)
  - Coordinated Beef Improvement Conference-1963 (Box 223, Folders 1-3)
  - Coordinated Beef Improvement Conference-1965, 1964 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - Coordinating Group of Commodity Association, 1977-1978 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - Roger Corbett Transcripts, undated (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - Corporate Farming-Non-Farm Interests, 1967-1976 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - Cow Culling, 1959 (Box 223, Folders 8-10)
  - Cowboys, 1955 (Box 223, Folder 11)
  - Credit, 1976-1980 (Box 223, Folder 12)
  - Credit-American Bankers Association, 1981 (Box 223, Folder 13)
  - Credit-Commercial Banks, 1981 (Box 223, Folder 14)
  - Credit-Controls, 1980 (Box 223, Folder 15)
  - Credit-Emergency Loans, 1977-1981 (Box 223, Folder 16)
  - Credit-Farm Credit Act Amendment of 1980, 1979-1981 (Box 223, Folders 17-21)
  - Credit-Farm Credit Act of 1971, 1979-1980 (Box 223, Folder 22)
  - Credit-Farm Credit Administration, 1981-1982 (Box 223, Folders 23-25)
  - Credit-Farm Credit Administration, 1981 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Credit-Farm Credit System, 1979-1981 (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - Credit-Farm Debt, 1976-1980 (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Credit-Farmers Home Administration, 1978-1982 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - Credit-Federal Reserve Board, 1980 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - Credit-Financing Agriculture, 1977, 1980 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Credit-Foreign Sources, 1980 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Credit-Innovations, 1980 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Credit-Interest Rates, 1979-1981 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - Credit-Laws, 1978 (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - Credit-Legislation, 1978-1980 (Box 224, Folder 11)
  - Credit-Livestock, 1978-1980 (Box 224, Folder 12)
  - Credit-Money Supply, 1978 (Box 224, Folder 13)
  - Credit-NOW Accounts, 1981 (Box 224, Folder 14)
  - Credit-Small Business Administration, 1977-1981 (Box 224, Folder 15)
  - Credit-Sources, 1981 (Box 224, Folder 16)
  - Credit-States, 1980 (Box 224, Folder 17)
  - Credit-Truth in Lending, 1980 (Box 224, Folder 18)
  - Credit-Usury Ceilings, 1980-1981 (Box 224, Folder 19)
  - Credit-Bills, 1975-1977 (Box 224, Folder 20)
  - Crop Report Release, News Availability Session, 1988 (Box 224, Folder 21)
  - Cunha, T.J, undated (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Dahlsten Truck Line Case, 1981 (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Dairyland Beef Association, 1986 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Dead Animals, 1965 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Debt and Foreign Aid, Publication-Our National Debt After Great Wars, 1946 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Debt and Foreign Aid, 1947 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - De Kalb Seminars, 1987 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Democratic National Convention-1964 (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - Denver Agricultural and Livestock Club, 1963, 1968 (Box 225, Folders 9-10)
  - Denver Chamber of Commerce, 1955-1965 (Box 225, Folders 11-12)
  - DES Case, 1980 (Box 225, Folder 13)
  - Desertification, 1980 (Box 225, Folder 14)
  - Diet/Health, 1979-1986 (Box 225, Folders 15-20)
  - Diet/Health, 1980-1987 (Box 226, Folders 1-3)
  - Diet/Health-Caster, Dr. W.O, 1977, 1982 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Diet/Health, 1982-1983, 1985-1986 (Box 226, Folders 5-8)
  - Diet/Health-Wolf, Isabel D., 1983-1984 (Box 226, Folder 9)
  - Dietary Goals, 1974, 1976-1981 (Box 226, Folders 10-15)
  - Dietary Goals, 1977-1978 (Box 227, Folders 1-8)
  - Dietary Goals, 1976-1981 (Box 228, Folders 1-9)
  - Dietary Goals, 1977-1979 (Box 229, Folders 1-7)
  - Dietary Goals, 1974-1981 (Box 230, Folders 1-8)
  - Dietary Goals, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Diethylstilbestrol (DES), 1976-1980 (Box 231, Folders 2-10)
  - Doane Survey, 1980 (Box 231, Folder 11)
  - Domestic Fats, 1932 (Box 231, Folder 12)
  - Dominick, Peter H., 1962-1963 (Box 231, Folder 13)
  - Dow Chemical Company, 1959-1961 (Box 231, Folders 14-16)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Beef and Cattle-Trends and Outlook, 1962-1974 (Box 232, Folders 1-2)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Budget Packet Information Requests, 1962-1966 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Buying, Selling, and Pricing-Cattle and Beef, 1967 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Cattle Feeding Budget Sheets, 1962 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Cattle Feeding Trends and Outlook, 1966-1974 (Box 232, Folders 6-7)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Comparative Price Trends, 1971-1972 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Cattle Production-Dates and Trends, 1971, 1973 (Box 232, Folder 9)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Contractual Farming, 1968 (Box 232, Folder 10)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Contract Selling, 1966 (Box 232, Folder 11)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Cost of Grain-Cattle, 1967-1974 (Box 232, Folder 12)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Economic Theories and Application, 1966-1967 (Box 232, Folder 13)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Farm Costs-General, 1967-1973 (Box 232, Folder 14)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Farm Income, 1965-1969 (Box 232, Folder 15)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Farm Prices and Inflation, 1966-1967, 1972, undated (Box 233, Folders 1-8)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Feed Consumed by Livestock, 1974 (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Feed Grains and Feedstuffs-Trends and Outlook, 1968-1973 (Box 233, Folder 10)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Feed Grain Production, 1966-1974 (Box 233, Folder 11)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Futures Market-Hedging, 1967-1977 (Box 233, Folder 12)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-General Economic Trends and Outlook, 1968-1975 (Box 233, Folders 13-14)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Integration-Livestock and Agriculture, 1965, 1968 (Box 233, Folder 15)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Livestock and Feed Grain Prices-Relationship, 1961 (Box 233, Folder 16)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Livestock Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 233, Folder 17)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Livestock Numbers and Inventory, 1960-1975 (Box 233, Folder 18)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Livestock on Feed, 1965-1968 (Box 233, Folder 19)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Livestock Processing-General, 1970 (Box 233, Folder 20)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Livestock Production, 1963-1974 (Box 233, Folder 21)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Livestock Slaughter, 1966-1970 (Box 233, Folder 22)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-“Low Man on the Totem Pole,”, 1962 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Marketing-General, 1966-1975 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Pork and Hogs-Trends and Outlook, 1966, 1968 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Pork Production, 1968, 1970 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Poultry Production, 1962 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Production Costs-Cattle, 1967, 1969 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Economic Data and Analysis-Range and Feed Conditions, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - Economic Recovery Tax Act, 1981 (Box 234, Folders 8-10)
  - Economic Stabilization, 1975-1976 (Box 234, Folder 11)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Cost of Living Council, 1973, 1975 (Box 234, Folder 12)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Economic Stabilization Act and Bills, 1973 (Box 234, Folder 13)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Economic Stabilization Legislation-1973, 1975 (Box 234, Folder 14)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Hearings-House Agriculture Committee, 1972 (Box 234, Folders 15-16)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Hearings-Price Committee, 1972 (Box 234, Folder 17)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Meat Price Information, 1971-1972 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Meat Price Information II, 1970-1972 (Box 235, Folders 2-4)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Meat Price Information III, 1972-1973 (Box 235, Folders 5-6)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Meat Price Information IV, 1972-1973 (Box 235, Folders 7-9)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Meat Price Information V, 1972-1973 (Box 235, Folder 10)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Meat Price Information VI, 1973 (Box 235, Folder 11)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Meat Price Information VI, 1973-1974 (Box 236, Folders 1-5)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Meat Price Information VII, 1972-1974 (Box 236, Folders 6-10)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Phase III-Wage-Price Program, 1972-1973 (Box 236, Folder 11)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Phase IV-Price Controls, 1973-1974 (Box 236, Folder 12)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Corr. And Information-Price Committee, 1972 (Box 236, Folder 13)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Price Info to Congress, 1973 (Box 236, Folder 14)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Regulations, Phase II-Food and Agriculture, 1971 (Box 236, Folder 15)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Regulations, Phase II-Food and Agriculture, 1972 (Box 237, Folders 1-2)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Regulations-Phase II-General, 1971-1972 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Regulations-Wage Price Freeze, 1971-1974 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Wage-Price Freeze, 1969-1971 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Phase II-Wage Price Freeze, 1971-1972 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - Economic Stabilization Program-Tax Amendments and Other Legislation, 1971 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - Elanco, 1984-1986 (Box 237, Folder 8)
  - Energy, 1977-1979 (Box 237, Folder 9)
  - Energy Bills, 1975-1976 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Enloe, Dr. Cortez, 1980-1981 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Control-Nebraska, 1970, 1973-1974 (Box 238, Folders 3-4)
  - Environmental Improvement, 1973 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Improvement-Animal Waste-American Society of Agricultural Engineering, 1973-1974 (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Improvement-Congressional Hearings, 1973 (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Improvement-Denver Conference, 1973 (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Improvement-House Conservation and Natural Resources Subcommittee, 1973 (Box 238, Folders 9-10)
  - Environmental Improvement-House Conservation and Natural Resources Subcommittee, 1973 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Improvement-NRDC-EPA Court Case, 1973-1974 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Improvement-National Commission on Water Quality, 1974 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Improvement-NRDC-EPA Court Case, 1973-1976 (Box 239, Folders 4-8)
  - Environmental Improvement-Pesticide Advisory Committee-EPA, 1974-1976 (Box 239, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Improvement-Bills to Amend-Pesticide Laws, etc., 1971 (Box 239, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Improvement-Pesticides, 1971-1977 (Box 239, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Improvement-Pesticides, 1963-1977 (Box 240, Folders 1-6)
  - Environmental Improvement-Pesticides II, 1973-1978 (Box 240, Folders 7-11)
  - Environmental Improvement-Pesticides Regulations, 1964-1977 (Box 240, Folders 12-16)
  - Environmental Improvement-Program Grants-EPA-Regulations, 1974 (Box 240, Folder 17)
  - Environmental Improvement-Regulations, 1973-1974 (Box 240, Folder 18)
  - Environmental Improvement-Waste Management Plans, Equipment, and Ideas, 1972-1977 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Improvement-Water Pollution, 1969-1977 (Box 241, Folders 2-10)
  - Environmental Improvement-Water Pollution, 1970s (Box 242, Folders 1-4)
  - Environmental Management-Agricultural Activity Standards I, 1973-1977 (Box 242, Folders 5-8)
  - Environmental Management-Ammonia, 1980 (Box 242, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Management-Dredge and Fill I, 1975-1977 (Box 242, Folders 10-14)
  - Environmental Management-Dredge and Fill II, 1975-1976 (Box 242, Folder 15)
  - Environmental Management-Dredge and Fill II, 1972-1976 (Box 243, Folders 1-4)
  - Environmental Management-Dredge and Fill III, 1976-1977 (Box 243, Folders 5-8)
  - Environmental Management-Federal Pollution Control Loan Program, 1976-1977 (Box 243, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Management-Feedlot Standards I, 1973-1974 (Box 243, Folders 10-13)
  - Environmental Management-Feedlot Standards III, 1975-1977 (Box 243, Folders 14-15)
  - Environmental Management-Feedlot Standards III, 1975-1977 (Box 244, Folders 1-2)
  - Environmental Management-Livestock Wastes, 1980 (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Management-Neb. Engineering Letter, 1975-1977 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Management-Toxaphene Position Paper, 1980 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Protection, 1972 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1971-1977 (Box 244, Folders 7-10)
  - Environmental Protection Agency-National Task Force-Animal Waste Management, 1972 (Box 244, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Protection Agency-State Legislation-Animal Waste Management, 1972, 1976 (Box 244, Folder 12)
  - Environmental Protection Agency-Clean Air, 1971-1972 (Box 244, Folder 13)
  - Environmental Protection Agency-Council on Environmental Quality, 1970-1971 (Box 244, Folder 14)